[Kim Hyeonseo as Sung Ho]
[Jung Myeongcheol as Yoo Sehyun]
[Kim Seonghyuk as Kwon Hyukjae]
[Jung Hyunwoong as Kim Minho]
[Sin and Love]
[Episode 8]
Wait!
Wait...
I'll do it!
I'll do it.
Hurry up.
Don't stall.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's not your fault.
Hey.
I said to kiss.
Never kissed before?
Exactly.
Enough.
Enough, Kwon Hyukjae.
Enough!
When will you stop,
huh?
Hey, you look pretty when you cry.
Enough, you jerk!
Hey, it's falling off.
Keep going
until Sung Ho's aroused.
Hey, did you hear that?
Sung Ho's body is quite honest.
Kwon Hyukjae,
you will go down.
Go down?
Do I look human to you?
What are you staring at?
Keep going.
I'm sorry.
Enough.
Please stop this, damn it.
Enough! Seriously...
So noisy.
Be quiet.
You're next.
Hey.
Hey!
Head up.
Head up!
Open your mouth.
How is it?
Good?
Minho's next.
Open up.
Open your mouth.
Okay!
Hey.
This is what teamwork is! Yeah?
Okay, okay.
Who is it?
-Hello...
-Hello, I'm from Korea Daily...
Was it you?
It's over.
It's your turn now.
-Hello.
I'm from Korea Daily.
We received a tip that
in this abandoned warehouse,
a kidnapping and violent assault
are taking place.
Don't move.
This is being broadcasted live.
It's over.
Why didn't you tell me?
To fool Kwon Hyukjae,
I had to fool you too.
Officer Kwon Hyukjae,
can you explain what's going on?
Okay.
We're done.
Hello, I'm from Korea Daily...
We're conducting tactical training.
It's a drill for undercover agents,
not a real incident.
I apologize
for the confusion caused.
But someone was tied up over there.
He's cooperating with the drill.
We're from the same squad.
You're such a great actor.
I thought it was real.
Good job.
What about all this blood?
As you can see,
it's fake blood.
Today's drill ends here.
If you're going to write articles,
base them on facts.
This was not a real act of violence,
but a drill.
P-Please leave now.
Damn it.
You...
You actually shot me.
How could you?
No.
I didn't want to kill you,
but just for it to graze you.
Because if I killed you,
it'd be over.
Don't do it again,
got it?
There won't be
a next time.
How did it feel when Kim Minho kissed you?
I was disgusted.
That's it?
Well...
his lips
were quite soft.
Still thinking about him?
About who?
Kim Minho.
I wasn't thinking about him.
I just...
find the situation weird.
Look only at me.
Right now?
From now on.
You look so anxious.
I almost died.
I almost never got to see you again.
So prove it to me right now.
How should I prove it?
We're in a hospital.
The door's locked.
Wait!
Does it hurt?
A little.
Even if it hurts,
I'm still happy.
Just now...
I was so happy when you called my name.
I called your name many times.
Do you love me a lot?
Very much.
You sure it's not just interest?
I love you.
Say it again.
Earlier,
when Kim Minho kissed you,
what were you thinking?
Well...
I wished it were you.
Liar.
It's true.
Really?
Really.
Really!
Got it.
Hug me.
What are you doing?
Lie down.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
Yoo Sehyun,
you're under arrest on suspicion of
illegal drug dealing at Gangnam Palace.
Please come with me.
[Sin and Love]